(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Extra Episode=
Welcome to the Ceramic Village.
You're all free to wander around today.
Besides buying some
souvenirs you like,
you also have a small mission.
Later, each of you will draw
a random name.
Then you need to give them a gift
that looks like them or suits them.
(Drawing cards)
Okay, draw one.
Come on, draw one.
Okay.
(Li Naiwen, Liu Yuning,
Deng Kai, Guo Jingfei)
(Yang Chaoyue, Wang Yuwen, Chen Xingxu, Sun Honglei)
Go ahead and start shopping.
(Picking gifts in the Ceramic Village)
A parrot toilet.
Just kidding.
It's for holding stuff.
This, 17th century.
It's more expensive
and complicated.
And this is from the 18th century.
They are different.
Eighteen?
That's the price, right?
What did she say?
I didn't catch it.
Sorry.
Can you repeat?
Yes.
This style is from the 17th century.
The King Louis XIV.
And this is from the 18th century.
The year.
The century.
Right, the 18th.
The 18th century.
The style from the 18th century.
And we made all these just upstairs.
She made these upstairs.
I made them.
I want these two.
(Buying them right away)
He wants to buy both of these.
Thank you.
I'll go check out other stores.
Okay.
This little cat is also cute.
This little cat is pretty cute too.
A little cat?
There are little cats.
Want to take a look?
Where are the little cats?
These are the ceramic little cats.
And standing little cats are over there.
This looks a lot like Chaoyue.
Let me compare.
It's really pretty.
(Loving it so much)
There's a second floor.
I'll go take a look.
That one-of-a-kind piece is really nice.
(Still thinking about the unique piece)
Because it...
Because it has a star.
The star hanging on it is right
between the two mountains,
representing the story
of the prisoner
from this town.
It's different.
(Wanting the unique piece)
I want this one.
(Xingxu wants it, Xingxu gets it)
I bought something I really like.
I'm so happy.
Because when I passed by just now,
I saw it.
It was so different.
It caught my eye immediately.
How to say "parrot"?
(Hesitating)
Well,
where did you see
that big ant for Deng Kai?
Just in that corner ahead.
I'll buy him a little pig too.
Alright.
There are two cicadas.
One for me,
and one for Honglei.
I love browsing such stores the most.
Because when I was a kid,
my father cooked for us all the time.
I often went grocery shopping with him.
(Awakening childhood memories)
Back then,
people usually got off work
around 5 or 6 PM.
Around 6 or 7 PM,
the leftover vegetables were cheaper.
I went there with my father to buy them.
So I have a soft spot for butcher shops.
Sometimes I get the urge to buy meat.
Look at the shop owner,
the lady.
She just looks like a fun person.
So as you can see, the things she sells
probably match her personality.
Interesting.
My daughter is eight and a half.
Which one do you recommend?
I want to buy her a book like this.
She says it's a gift for you.
Thank you very much.
- It's a gift.
- For your daughter.
Okay, thank you.
I think I should buy something.
Let me pick one.
I'm so touched.
Look at her, getting on in years,
but her eyes are incredibly pure.
She must be a very special
artist,
because her work has so much soul.
This is very special. This pendant.
Okay.
Check, please.
Together.
Thank you very much.
My gift.
I think this cup is really pretty.
Doesn't this look like Jingfei?
Is this handmade?
And there's only one, right?
I'll take this one.
Okay.
Yes.
My favorite.
Thank you very much.
So cute.
I think this looks like you.
It does look a bit like me.
Pretty.
Okay.
This one. This is you.
I think this is really pretty.
Right.
Actually, this lamp is also...
This lamp is really pretty.
Yuning.
Which is better?
They're both nice.
This one is more artsy.
I don't know.
(Let me think about it)
This one.
What did you buy?
A plate.
I'll buy a plate.
This one looks great.
I think the pattern
is beautifully drawn.
This looks exactly like my clown
from that day.
Looks like it,
right?
It does.
Thank you.
This is indeed
pretty cute.
It has a function.
It's also a scented sachet.
Nice.
Only...
only rabbits and bears.
I think this is a great gift.
It's also practical.
These are so well-made.
The keychains.
Is this a bottle opener?
I'm paying now.
This is Chaoyue.
Bonjour.
Hello.
This kid is fun.
Are you a famous person in China?
Everyone is recording.
In China,
I'm very famous.
You?
I'm a movie star.
Movie star?
Yes.
And a dancer and a singer.
I was bragging.
I left them speechless.
Where are you from?
I'm from the Netherlands.
The Netherlands.
Amsterdam.
Goodbye.
Have a nice day.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
I bragged so hard that they all ran off.
They got embarrassed.
It's fine, as long
as I'm not embarrassed.
Let's go.
I'm so happy.
I find bragging
is quite stress-relieving.
He wants to search for you online.
It's fine.
Oh, no, I'm busted now.
If they search me online, I'm done for.
Thank you very much.
Have a nice day.
Did you tell him?
Otherwise, the guy will say,
"Why did that dude brag to me?"
He'll get mad and come back to verify.
I've noticed you really
love shopping, Xingxu.
No.
I only love browsing...
I only love browsing really local stuff.
The very special stuff.
Scenic spots. Just scenic spots.
Please share the gifts you bought.
I drew Honglei.
Really?
Yes.
(Gift for Sun Honglei: a golden cicada)
Two golden cicadas.
One is mine, and one is yours.
It represents our character.
Because
the cicada has a special meaning
in this town.
Also, in China,
it represents gentlemen.
It represents men of honor.
It reminds us both to stay true
to our original aspirations,
to keep making truly good works,
and to thank and serve the audience.
One golden cicada for you.
It also foreshadows
our upcoming collaboration.
Thank you.
Let's keep our original aspirations
and be good creators.
The heart of a gentleman.
Thank you.
Is it pure gold?
Pure copper.
I personally believe it's gold.
(Heartfelt)
Okay.
Alright.
My turn, right?
First,
I passed by a shop.
This one.
A lavender shop.
We can also buy this back home,
but I felt like since we're in
the Land of Lavender,
I had to buy one.
Right.
So I bought one for everyone.
Here, one for you.
Here.
One for you.
Thank you.
- One for you.
- Thank you.
Alright.
- I bought a bear for everyone.
- Thank you.
A souvenir.
- Alright.
This little bear is so cute.
Thank you.
Alright.
Lavender-scented.
Yes.
Smells so good.
I drew Xingxu.
Yes.
So I bought Xingxu a plate.
(Gift for Chen Xingxu: a ceramic plate)
This plate is really great.
I think it's the most beautiful
plate in that shop.
Great.
So what is it?
Actually,
I thought a lot.
Because he likes coffee.
I thought about a coffee cup.
But I felt like in last season,
we were all gifting cups.
So I thought
I should get something different.
So I bought you
a beautifully painted plate.
Awesome.
It's hand-painted.
But what's the most important?
The most important thing is
that on it, there's
a unicorn-like sheep.
Because you're an Aries, right?
I'm a bit touched.
And below it,
there's a clown playing music.
(Exactly what Xingxu wanted)
This is so beautiful.
Yes.
The clown is the role I played that day.
There's one last meaning.
I hope you
eat more delicious food.
And taste all the world's cuisines.
Okay?
Thank you.
This plate is really beautiful.
It's so beautiful.
As expected,
Yuning is the best at "pan".
What do you mean by that?
He's always rubbing his bracelet beads.
[*"Plate" and "rubbing" are both "pan"]
He "pan" everything.
He loves it and is good at it.
What a coincidence.
No coincidence, no story.
I drew Jingfei.
I think Jingfei is
a very, very good actor.
And I've told him that in private.
I chose for a long time.
I checked three shops
and picked this cup.
(Gift for Guo Jingfei: a ceramic cup)
I think this is the Jingfei in my heart.
The thing is, this one is too.
They both look like
they've eaten a lot of cake.
It's obvious.
Right.
I hope he can be like this cup,
able to hold
lots and lots of water,
different kinds of water,
and play many, many roles,
different kinds of roles.
This is so pretty.
(A heavy heart)
Thank you.
It's pretty.
Did you also buy it from that old lady?
No.
Another shop.
It's handmade. I asked.
There's only one.
It's really a cup?
Yes.
It can hold fruit wine, juice,
plain water,
or beer. Anything is fine.
It's beautiful. Thank you.
It's pretty.
I drew Yuwen.
We browsed that shop together.
This is a little rabbit.
Because I think
in my heart, Yuwen is
a very cute little animal.
I thought she was
a lot like a quokka.
But there wasn't one.
So I think this rabbit
suits her too.
Yuwen is just
naturally approachable.
And she's an air sign.
When she's around,
I feel really at ease.
So I think
a little animal represents Yuwen best.
Thank you, Chaoyue.
When we went to that shop,
I said I wanted one of each,
the bear and the rabbit.
Then Chaoyue said
she thought I was rabbit-like,
and she bought me a rabbit.
I was like,
"Okay, I won't buy the rabbit then
since Chaoyue will give me one."
And when I saw that little bear,
I said, "Forget it. I won't buy it."
But then Yuning gave me one.
Wish fulfillment.
Really.
See?
They make a pair.
I drew Chaoyue.
This looks so much like her.
(Let me see)
It's on the surface.
Yes.
I picked this ceramic owl.
Pretty, very pretty.
So pretty.
Pretty. Very delicate.
Very delicate.
And
because I know Chaoyue
has bird-like features.
(You noticed that?)
Bird-like features?
Bird-coded.
Yes.
So I wanted to pick
something bird-related.
Bird-related.
Both a cat and a bird.
(Both cat-coded and bird-coded)
Yes.
So I chose this owl.
[*Owl is "cat-head eagle" in Chinese]
Owl.
Very pretty. Pretty.
Pretty.
The color is also great.
For protection.
(Showing off)
My turn.
(Drew Deng Kai to pick a gift for)
I'm the worst at shopping.
I don't like shopping either.
I don't know how to shop.
So
I was single-mindedly
thinking about Deng Kai.
But honestly,
for Deng Kai,
I don't know him that well.
Right?
Yes.
So I used the dumbest method.
I searched.
Deng Kai was born
in the year of the pig.
(Did his homework)
So,
I bought him a little pig.
(Gift for Deng Kai)
Great.
And it's also a piggy bank.
I think a piggy bank
has a meaning too.
Right?
Yes.
I need to save more money.
(Advice from a senior)
Spend wisely.
Yes, I will.
I got it.
Some little advice from a senior.
At the same time,
I actually bought another little thing.
(More?)
Because when we talked
in the car yesterday,
he said he doesn't eat or sleep
at regular times.
I really feel for this kid.
I also feel for
your parents.
(Comprehensive care)
What I mean is,
your mom won't even need
to call you for meals.
(Bell summoning technique)
She can just...
Time to eat.
It's to make you eat on time.
Thank you.
This is nice.
This is so cute.
This is basically for your parents.
Thank you.
And then?
There's more?
For someone who is bad at shopping,
I bought quite a lot.
Also, just now,
actually, Kai...
I don't know why he'd like this.
The big ant.
You really bought it for me?
Yes.
He said this ant looks a lot like him.
Thin
and skinny.
But I think an ant
has a meaning too.
Because an ant
is small in size
but huge in energy.
Yes.
Well, I've
worked with Kai on a drama before.
And I've also seen his acting.
Well,
don't be fooled by how skinny Kai is.
He has a lot of energy.
He can portray different characters.
So this ant suits you perfectly.
I've decided to give it to you.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
(As long as you like it)
I drew Yuning.
Yuning said
he has a song
called A Little Light on Ordinary Days.
So I kept searching.
I asked if there were any candles
or lamps.
Then I found a lamp shop.
(Gift for Liu Yuning: ceramic desk lamp)
This lamp is pretty.
It's pretty.
This is really pretty.
And the light
couldn't be too bright
since it's "a little light".
Then in that corner,
I found this lamp.
It has a hot air balloon on it,
with a person in it.
I know Yuning is afraid of heights.
So I'm giving him this
so he'll never be afraid again.
Thank you.
It's pretty.
It matches your outfit a bit.
It really does.
I will hold it up as I walk.
(Getting a fashion item)
I think it's the most beautiful
lamp in that shop.
It's pretty.
You can give me the plug.
Why?
I can always generate power for you.
Generate power for you.
You're like a pop-pop firework.
Pop-pop firework.
I drew Nai.
I think this suits Nai perfectly.
What is it?
(A mysterious ring)
What is this?
A rolling hoop?
A hula hoop?
You didn't just pick it up, did you?
Is this something you bought?
Yes, of course.
(What did my ears just hear?)
How could it be picked up?
What the heck?
Now I'm Nezha.
It's actually a set.
I thought it was a rolling hoop
- to remind you of your childhood.
- I thought so too.
It's a...
I think it's very...
In the shop, it's indeed
(The essence is here)
- a one-of-a-kind colored parrot.
- A bird.
This is pretty.
The color is so vivid.
It's beautiful.
Yes, beautiful.
About the parrot...
Why would I give it to Nai?
Because I think he's like a parrot.
He's wise and mighty.
[*It puns on "wise and mighty" in Chinese]
(Wise and mighty)
That's how I feel about him.
And
the parrot
is also very eloquent.
(Eloquent)
(Feeling flattered)
Just like Nai.
That is true.
It's like his personality on our show.
It's hanging.
It's pretty.
(Gift for Li Naiwen: ceramic parrot)
Really pretty.
You can take the bird
for a walk in the park.
Its color is also
one-of-a-kind in that shop.
There isn't another one.
First, there are no other
hanging parrot ornaments.
Second,
every one they made
is different.
It's pretty.
Really pretty.
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪That day, we left on a hard road♪
♪In countless late nights,
we exchanged courage♪
♪Our fates have already intertwined♪
♪In each other's life trajectories♪
♪We leave behind
bonds like no other for a lifetime♪
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪Traveling around the earth♪
♪Tasting all the freshness♪
♪Having traveled all corners♪
♪We still stand shoulder to shoulder♪
♪I'm glad to have met you♪
♪We hum melodiously♪
♪Always trying to write with you♪
♪Thankfully we still share the same sky♪